Kevin Harris

Senior Full-Stack & Blockchain Engineer

I am an experienced senior full-stack developer who has been mainly focusing on JavaScript, Python, C/C++ and Java to develop the products.

During the last 6+ years, I have worked in many companies to build applications for people all over the world. As an active and innovative learner, I love learning new programming languages and skills.

I have rich experience in blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies as well for DeFi application. I fully guarantee my code quality and I am eager to brainstorm a new idea with teammates.

My goal is to offer more products that people would prefer.

Contact Infomation



nike.dragon0905@gamil.com



S live:.cid.db7376c3cccdf9af

NikeDragon#9783

Education

National University of Singapore

(2013 - 2017, GPA: 3.7/4.0)

Degree: Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc)

Skills

Programming Language:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Python, C/C++, Java, NodeJS

Styling Lanuage:

Bootstrap, SCSS, LESS, Tailwind CSS

Front-end Framework

React, Vue.js, Angular, Next.js

Back-end Framework

Laravel, ExpressJS, Django, Ruby on Rail, SpringBoot

Database

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Oracle, Elasticsearch

No-Coding Platform

WordPress, Shopify, Webflow

Work Experience

Senior Front-end & Blockchain Engineer

PowerUSD, LLC - United States (Feb 2022 - Feb 2023)

- Developed smart contracts for decentralized lending platform on Ethereum blockchain and integrated with Front-end using web3
- Worked on Golang Backend API service
- Audited smart contracts for NFT tokens and sales on Polygon/Matic
- Ensured quality standards through regular code reviews of contractor's codebase contributions
- Tech Stack: Blockchain, Ethereum, web3, React, Redux, Golang, Polygon/Matic

Senior Full-stack Engineer

Golden Hippo - United States (Oct 2020 - Dec 2021)

- Worked with a team of senior web designers, full-stack engineers, and the QAs to meet project goals and create effective user experiences for millions of subscribers
- Developed full-stack applications across various platforms using the latest industry-adopted technologies and frameworks
- Worked using CMS Frameworks and no-coding platforms
- Ported the underlying deprecated Ionic library to Webpack 5, speeding up local and remote builds by up to six times
- Worked mainly on front-end and reported the progress of the project to PM(Project Manager) weekly
- Participated in the development of API for payment between B2B, B2C, and C2C
- Worked on an agile team and presented my idea for the product to CEO in the scrum meeting
- Tech Stack: Next, React Native, TypeScript, Prisma, NodeJS, ExpressJS, WordPress, Webflow, Shopify, openAPI, EtherJS, Solana

Full-stack Developer

Coding Dojo- United States (Dec 2019 - Sep 2020)

- Developed dynamic and interactive websites that ensured high traffic, page views, and user experience, resulting in 40% increase in sales revenue
- Oversaw the full lifecycle of software development for 4 projects with 100% on-time delivery while staying 5% under budget

Blockchain:

Smart Contract, Ethereum, Web3

Code Management Tools:

GitHub, Beyond Compare

Testing Tools:

Jest, Enzyme, Moca, Cypress

OS:

Windows, MacOS, Linux, Unix

DevOps:

CI/CD, IAC, Monitoring/Feedback, Collaboration/Com

DevOps:

CI/CD, IAC, Monitoring/Feedback, Collaboration/Com

Other:

Data Structure & Algorithm, Network Security, Artificial Intelligence

Language

English

Native / Bilingual Proficiency

Chinese

Fluent

Hobby

Tennis Piano

Swimming Guitar

Basketball

- Added to the company database of code by developing reusable code that could minimize the time needed to maintain the projects
- Designed and developed product details page by using React for user interface, SASS, Material UI for styling, and Redux for state management
- Implemented server with various databases (RDBMS and NoSQL) for retrieving the data in the form of JSON using AJAX
- Used Git version control for the source code management of the application
- Tech Stack: React, SASS, ExpressJS, REST, AWS, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Web Developer Intern

Forest Company - Hong Kong (Jun 2017 - Nov 2019)

- Designed the Web application layout and forms
- Handled all the client-side validations, slide show, hide/show controls, dropdown menus, and tab navigation using jQuery
- Wrote application-level code to perform client-side validations using jQuery and JavaScript
- Used SVN for version control and defect tracking
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility issues and fix the bugs pertaining to various browsers
- Pair programmed with 2 engineers and reviewed the team's code to provide additional perspective and catch previously missed errors
- Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, MySQL

Certifications

- HTML5 Web Developer Camp Certificate in 2018
- Front-end Web Development Certificate in 2019
- Full-stack Web and Multiplatform App Development Certificate in 2020
- IBM Blockchain Foundation for Developer by IBM on Coursera in 2021